RAKUL R SAMPATH

61, Barnwell Woods, Hansfield, Dublin 15, D15CA2N, Ireland

(+353) 892235325 | rsrakul94@outlook.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT

An energetic and devoted Engineer with proven success to deliver high results in multi-national organization. Individual establishment incorporates a Bachelors in Electronics and Instrumentation Engineering and a Masters in Internet of Things (present) with 3 year of work experience. Seeking to secure a responsible position to fully utilize my expertise and skills, while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.

EDUCATION

MEng. - Internet of Things Technologies

TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY DUBLIN

Dublin, Ireland *Sep.2019-Sep.2020

B.E. - Electronics and Instrumentation Engineering

HINDUSTHAN COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY | CGPA 7.59/10

Coimbatore, India Aug. 2012-Apr. 2016

EXPERIENCE

IVTL Infoview Technologies

Chennai, India

TEST ENGINEER

July 2016 – Sep.2019

- Performing Web Application Testing for ERP software applications which are used in HR Management and Payroll sectors
- Worked in Agile, Functional testing, Regression testing, Sanity, System Integration and User Acceptance in Exploratory/Scripted testing approach.
- Good Knowledge in understanding software and writing detailed test case document and providing timely information to development team and client.

Thalapakatti Restaurant

Coimbatore, India

FOOD PACKAGING & SERVING EXECUTIVE

Oct. 2015 - Jun.2016

- Cleaning crockery & cutlery and ensuring food preparation sites are clean and ready.
- Ensuring the storeroom remains organized.
- Making sure work surfaces, floors and walls are always clean and sanitized.

SKILLS PROFILE

Computer Languages

C, C++

Tools

MS Office, Apache Open Office

CORE SKILLS

Leadership and Teamwork Flexibility and Adaptable Excellent IT skills

EXTRA-CURRICULARS

Member of Technological University Dublin Cricket club Member of Technological University Dublin Volunteering

INTERESTS

Cricket

Volleyball